

Eslam Hugair

FullStack web developer

e.eslam3bed@gmail.com

+970592545262

Gaza, Palestine

eslam.dev

linkedin.com/in/eslam3bed in

github.com/Eslam3bed 🚺

I'm an experienced full-stack web developer, with more than 5 years of working experience. I've developed and maintained e2e applications and mobile-friendly websites. Strongly committed to all projects from inception right through to the end, focusing on front-end frameworks, to build interactive web applications with rich user experience.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Sr. Front End developer

weart.io 🗷

02/2022 - Present

Development Agency, that focus on making quality products.

full stack web developer

LeadCart.io 🗷

09/2018 - 01/2022 Delaware, USA

Cart Solution Startup focuses on increasing booting the conversions for customer sales using targeted funnels.

- Achievements/Tasks
- Built a custom components design system to fulfill the company design requirements.
- Built utility packages for reusable functionalities.
- Developed multiple versions of a checkout forms/page builder at multiple iterations.
- Handling DevOps for the company products using Githbub actions automation & AWS cloud services, with
 > 0.1% downtime for the products.
- Became the team lead, and CTO of the startup a year after joining the startup team.

full stack web developer Zaino

05/2016 - 09/2019

Nazareth, Palestine

A platform that intends to enhance the Adword customer user experience with the support of templates and other optimizations.

- Achievements/Tasks
- Built the product user interfaces, and its APIs to support the core application functionalities.
- Build an administration dashboard to control the application settings and preferences.
- Designed and developed a customer support widget to onboard customers to thez application.

Front end web developer

Freelancer 05/2016 - 10/2018

Remote

working on different types of applications, including web applications, chrome extensions.

- Achievements/Tasks
- Build "Tawasol" a web application for a local IT company, with native front-end technologies.
- Building a Dropshipping consultant chrome extension.
- Building a lead magnet kit for a local client.

SKILLS



VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

O Quality Assurance Gaza Sky Geeks

06/2018 - 10/2018

Gaza. Palestine

a program of Mercy Corps, a leading global humanitarian agency working on some of the world's toughest challenges.

- Tasks/Achievements

- Code reviews & Mentoring

Contact: https://gazaskygeeks.com/contact/

EDUCATION

O A Bachelor's degree in Software Engineering

University Of Palestine

02/2012 - 06/2017

LANGUAGES

Arabic

English

Full Professional Proficiency Pro

Professional Working Proficiency

INTERESTS

Blockchain

ΔΙ

Cryptocurrencies